Guide to the Records of the New York University Photo Bureau RG.7.2.2
New York University Archives
Records of the New York University Photo Bureau
1952-2014
New York University Archives
New York University. Photo Bureau
RG.7.2.2
111.75 Linear Feet in 183 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, 3 media boxes, 19 record cartons, 2 flat boxes, 3 oversize flat boxes, and 1 oversize folder in shared housing
250.29 Gigabytes
The NYU Photo Bureau offers photographic services to the New York University (NYU) community through portraits of staff, students, and trustees, many of which are used in NYU-related publications and marketing material. These records contain images, NYU printed matter, and administrative files for the NYU Photo Bureau Department, dating from 1952 and 1970 to 2009.
Conditions Governing Access
Administrative records and unpublished reports of New York University are closed for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation. Access to files spanning multiple years will be opened to researchers based on the date of the most recent materials. Board of Trustees records are closed for 35 years from the date of creation. Materials related to personnel, grievances, job and fellowship searches and applications, and all files that fall under the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) are permanently restricted. Additional restrictions may apply to other materials in this collection. For questions regarding specific restrictions, please contact the University Archives.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred from the Photo Bureau in 1996, 2009-2011, 2013, 2015, 2018-2020. The accession numbers associated with these transfers are 96.016, 96.019, 09.005, 09.018, 10.022, 11.008, 11.015, 11.025, 13.034, 15.040, 2019.015, 2019.095, and 2020.014.
Arrangement
Information on the arrangement of the material before the 2019 accretion is not documented at this time.
In 2019, contact sheets were arranged in original order as one series.
For the 2019.015 accretion, this accretion has not been arranged by an archivist. The materials are arranged in the order in which they were received from the donor.
For the 2019.095 accretion, discs were arranged in chronological order.
Historical Note
The NYU Photo Bureau offers photographic services to the New York University community including Dean, Trustee, and student portrait sessions; organizing photo shoots for events; copyright/licensing; stock photo purchases; and photo archiving.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Advance notice is required for the use of computer records. Original physical digital media is restricted.
Born-digital materials have not been transferred and may not be available to researchers. Researchers may request access copies. To request that material be transferred, or if you are unsure if material has been transferred, please contact the University Archives at university-archives@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Scope and Contents
Images in the form of print photographs, digital files, slides, contact sheets, and negatives of NYU faculty and staff, students, parents, alumni, and student life on and off campus are in this collection. Printed material in this collection consists of NYU brochures, newspapers, bulletins, and viewbooks for NYU Departments. Also in this collection are files related to the administration of this department and include schedules as well as correspondence for photoshoots of professors, deans, trustees and students. Files containing waivers and headshots for student models can also be found in this collection.
Contact sheets.; Photographs.; Color slides.; Promotional materials; College students -- New York (N.Y.); Schedules (time plans); Digital images.; New York University. Photo Bureau
- Contact Sheets, 1956-2007; 65.5 Linear Feet in 130 manuscript boxes and 3 oversize flat boxes
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of color and black and white contact sheets and some negatives grouped and dated by the NYU Photo Bureau. Original order and folder information have been maintained.
  - Contact Sheets 7545-9982 (odd numbering system): 44-3001 (Box 2)
  - Contact Sheets 3092-4399 (Box 2A)
  - Contact Sheets 4403-4998 (Box 3)
  - Contact Sheets 5000-6181 (Box 4)
  - Contact Sheets 6182-8057 (Box 5)
  - Contact Sheets Unnumbered, 8061-9151 (Box 6)
  - Contact Sheets 9152-9223 (Box 7)
  - Contact Sheets 9224-9324 (Box 8)
  - Contact Sheets 9325-9470 (Box 9)
  - Contact Sheets Unnumbered, 9471 to 9565-3Z (Box 10)
  - Contact Sheets 9565-4A to 9643 (Box 11)
  - Contact Sheets: Unnumbered (Alan Orling); 9645-9712 (Box 12)
  - Contact Sheets 86-001 to 86-104 (Box 13)
  - Contact Sheets 86-105 to 86-238 (Box 14)
  - Contact Sheets 86-239 to 86-365 (Box 15)
  - Contact Sheets 86-366 to 86-457 (Box 16)
  - Contact Sheets 86-458 to 86-544 (Box 17)
  - Contact Sheets 87-025 to 87-099 (Box 18)
  - Contact Sheets 87-100 to 87-189 (Box 19)
  - Contact Sheets 87-190 to 87-299 (Box 20)
  - Contact Sheets 87-300 to 87-394 (Box 21)
  - Contact Sheets 87-396 to 87-465 (Box 22)
  - Contact Sheets 87-466 to 87-599 (Box 23)
  - Contact Sheets 88-019 to 88-080 (Box 24)
  - Contact Sheets 88-082 to 88-209 (Box 25)
  - Contact Sheets 88-210 to 88-316 (Box 26)
  - Contact Sheets 88-317 to 88-392 (Box 27)
  - Contact Sheets 88-393 to 89-006G (Box 28)
  - Contact Sheets 89-006H to 89-081 (Box 29)
  - Contact Sheets 89-082 to 89-169 (Box 30)
  - Contact Sheets 89-170 to 89-220 (Box 31)
  - Contact Sheets 89-221 to 89-286 (Box 32)
  - Contact Sheets 89-287 to 89-370 (Box 33)
  - Contact Sheets 89-370 to 89-422 (Box 34)
  - Contact Sheets 89-423 to 90-030 (Box 35)
  - Contact Sheets 90-031 to 90-115 (Box 36)
  - Contact Sheets 90-116 to 90-205 (Box 37)
  - Contact Sheets 90-206 to 90-324 (Box 38)
  - Contact Sheets 90-325 to 90-352 (Box 39)
  - Contact Sheets 90-353 to 90-418 (Box 40)
  - Contact Sheets 90-420 to 90-489 (Box 41)
  - Contact Sheets 90-490 to 91-062 (Box 42)
  - 91-063 to 91-153 (Box 43)
  - 91-154 to 91-193 (Box 44)
  - 91-195 to 91-295 (Box 45)
  - 91-296 to 91-349 (Box 46)
  - 91-350 to 91-453 (Box 47)
  - 91-454 to 92-021 (Box 48)
  - 92-023 to 92-103 (Box 49)
  - 92-104 to 92-189 (Box 50)
  - 92-190 to 92-269 (Box 51)
  - 92-270 to 92-362 (Box 52)
  - 92-363 to 92-413 (Box 53)
  - 92-414 to 92-508 (Box 54)
  - 92-509 to 92-534 (Box 55)
  - 92-535 to 93-076 (Box 56)
  - 93-077 to 93-169 (Box 57)
  - 93-170 to 93-250 (Box 58)
  - 93-251 to 93-336 (Box 59)
  - 93-337 to 93-415 (Box 60)
  - 93-417 to 93-467 (Box 61)
  - 93-468 to 94-042 (Box 62)
  - 94-043 to 94-140 (Box 63)
  - 94-141 to 94-200 (Box 64)
  - 94-201 to 94-271 (Box 65)
  - 94-272 to 94-315 (Box 66)
  - 94-316 to 94-365 (Box 67)
  - 94-367 to 94-431 (Box 68)
  - 94-432 to 94-494 (Box 69)
  - 94-495 to 95-022 (Box 70)
  - 95-024 to 95-090 (Box 71)
  - 95-091 to 95-161 (Box 72)
  - 95-162 to 95-239 (Box 73)
  - 95-240 to 95-279, 95-307 to 95-368 (Box 74)
  - 95-369 to 95-445 (Box 75)
  - 95-455 to 95-513 (Box 76)
  - 95-515 to 96-024 (Box 77)
  - 96-025 to 96-122 (Box 78)
  - 96-123 to 96-220 (Box 79)
  - 96-221 to 96-309 (Box 80)
  - 96-310 to 96-384 (Box 81)
  - 96-385 to 96-451 (Box 82)
  - 96-452 to 96-529 (Box 83)
  - 96-531 to 96-599 (Box 84)
  - 96-601 to 96-651 (Box 85)
  - 96-652 to 97-040 (Box 86)
  - 97-041 to 97-120 (Box 87)
  - 97-121 to 97-208 (Box 88)
  - 97-209 to 97-281 (Box 89)
  - 97-282 to 97-357 (Box 90)
  - 97-358 to 97-434 (Box 91)
  - 97-435 to 97-497 (Box 92)
  - 97-498 to 97-563 (Box 93)
  - 97-564 to 98-039 (Box 94)
  - 98-040 to 98-115 (Box 95)
  - 98-117 to 98-195 (Box 96)
  - 98-196 to 98-268 (Box 97)
  - 98-269 to 98-350 (Box 98)
  - 98-351 to 98-407 (Box 99)
  - 98-408 to 98-470 (Box 100)
  - 98-471 to 98-505 (Box 101)
  - 98-506 to 98-567 (Box 102)
  - 98-569 to 98-635 (Box 103)
  - 00-201 to 00-312 (Box 105)
  - 00-313 to 00-404 (Box 106)
  - 00-405 to 00-491 (Box 107)
  - 00-492 to 00-572 (Box 108)
  - 00-574 to 01-050 (Box 109)
  - 01-051 to 01-171 (Box 110)
  - 01-172 to 01-678 (Box 111)
  - 01-645 to 01-765 (Box 112)
  - 01-766 to 01-838 (Box 113)
  - 01-839 to 01-946 (Box 114)
  - 01-947 to 02-041 (Box 115)
  - 02-042 to 02-186 (Box 116)
  - 02-188 to 02-339 (Box 117)
  - 02-340 to 02-464 (Box 118)
  - 02-466 to 02-588 (Box 119)
  - Contact Sheets 99-003 to 99-057 (Box 120)
  - Contact Sheets 99-060 to 99-136 (Box 121)
  - 99-138 to 99-230 (Box 122)
  - 99-231 to 99-276 (Box 123)
  - Contact Sheets 99-278 to 99-360 (Box 124)
  - 99-361 to 99-432 (Box 125)
  - 99-434 to 99-499 (Box 126)
  - 99-500 to 99-560 (Box 127)
  - 00-105 to 00-200 (Box 128)
  - 00-002 to 00-059 (Box 129)
  - 03-001 to 03-041C, 03-117, 03-119, 03-160, 03-186, 03-239, 03-249, 03-254, 03-260,03-294, 03-436, 03-468, 03-560, 04-284, 04-643, 05-190 to 05-192, 05-393, 05-426, 05-456, 05-458, 06-455, 07-144 (Box 131)
  - 00-060A to 00-104C (Box 132)
  - Oversize Contact Sheets, 2-1433 - 3-2083, 95-256 C-E (Box 133, Folder 1-4)
  - Oversize Contact Sheets, 3-6038 - 3-9862 (Box 134, Folder 1-4)
  - Oversize Contact Sheets, 89-106 - 01-102 (Box 135, Folder 1-11)
- Negatives, 1952-2007
  - Negatives 4/1 to 4/296, 1952 (Box 202)
  - Negatives 4/297 to 4/779, 1952-1953 (Box 203)
  - Negatives 4/780 to 4/2118, 1953 (Box 204)
  - Negatives 4/2119 to 4/2676, 1953-1954 (Box 205)
  - Negatives 4/2677 to 4/3049, 1954 (Box 206)
  - Negatives 4/3050 to 4/3430, 1954 (Box 207)
  - Negatives 4/3431 to 4/3899, 1954 (Box 208)
  - Negatives 4/3922 to 4/4429, 1954-1955 (Box 209)
  - Negatives 4/4430 to 4/4750, 1955 (Box 210)
  - Negatives 4/4751 to 4/4900, 1955-1956 (Box 211)
  - Negatives 4/4901 to 4/5070, 1956 (Box 212)
  - Negatives 4/5071 to 4/5248, 1956 (Box 213)
  - Negatives 2/5249 to 4/5400, 1956-1957 (Box 214)
  - Negatives 4/5401 to 2/5539, 1957 (Box 215)
  - Negatives 4/5540 to 4/5705, 1957 (Box 216)
  - Negatives 4/5706 to 4/5880, 1957 (Box 217)
  - Negatives 4/5881 to 4/6065, 1957-1958 (Box 218)
  - Negatives 2/6066 to 4/6223, 1958 (Box 219)
  - Negatives 4/6224 to 4/6395, 1958 (Box 220)
  - Negatives 4/6396 to 4/6560, 1958-1959 (Box 221)
  - Negatives 3/6561 to 4/6743, 1959 (Box 222)
  - Negatives 4/6744 to 3/6905, 1959 (Box 223)
  - Negatives 3/6906 to 3/7030, 1959-1960 (Box 224)
  - Negatives 2/7031 to 3/7175, 1960 (Box 225)
  - Negatives 2/7176 to 4/7353, 1960 (Box 226)
  - Negatives 4/7354 to 2/7510, 1960 (Box 227)
  - Negatives 4/7511 to 3/7665, 1960-1961 (Box 228)
  - Negatives 3/7666 to 4/7827, 1961 (Box 229)
  - Negatives 3/7828 to 3/7984A-C, 1961 (Box 230)
  - Negatives 4/7986 to 4/8126, 1961 (Box 231)
  - Negatives 4/8127 to 3/8270 A-I, 1961-1962 (Box 232)
  - Negatives 3/8270A-R to 3/8392A-D, 1962 (Box 233)
  - Negatives 2/8393 to 3/8521, 1962 (Box 234)
  - Negatives 4/8522 to 4/8649 A-E, 1962 (Box 235)
  - Negatives 2/8650 to 3/8783 A-C, 1962-1963 (Box 236)
  - Negatives 3/8784 to 3/8910, 1963 (Box 237)
  - Negatives 3/8911 A-C to 4/9000, 1963 (Box 238)
  - Negatives 3/9001A-E to 4/9091, 1963 (Box 239)
  - Negatives 3/9092 A-P to 3/9194, 1963 (Box 240)
  - Negatives 3/9195 to 2/9301, 1963-1964 (Box 241)
  - Negatives 2/9302 to 4/9410, 1964 (Box 242)
  - Negatives 4/9411 to 3/9540A-B, 1964 (Box 243)
  - Negatives 3/9541 to 3/9604, 1964 (Box 244)
  - Negatives 3/9605A-C to 4/9716, 1964 (Box 245)
  - Negatives 4/9717 to 4/9809, 1964 (Box 246)
  - Negatives 4/9810 to 4/9930, 1964-1965 (Box 247)
  - Negatives 4/9931 to 3/5 A-G, 1965 (Box 248)
  - Negatives 3/6 to 3/101E-H, 1965 (Box 249)
  - Negatives 2/102 to 2/200, 1965 (Box 250)
  - Negatives 3/201A-C to 4/297, 1965 (Box 251)
  - Negatives 4/299 to 4/399, 1965 (Box 252)
  - Negatives 4/400 to 3/485A-F, 1965 (Box 253)
  - Negatives 3/286A-G to 3/544A-B, 1965-1966 (Box 254)
  - Negatives 3/546 to 4/644, 1966 (Box 255)
  - Negatives 3/645A-F to 3/730A-E, 1966 (Box 256)
  - Negatives 3/731 A-G to 4/806, 1966 (Box 257)
  - Negatives 3/807 to 3/864A-E, 1966 (Box 258)
  - Negatives 3/865 to 3/937A-G, 1966 (Box 259)
  - Negatives 3/938A-D to 4/999, 1966 (Box 260)
  - Negatives 3/1001 to 4/1122, 1966-1967 (Box 261)
  - Negatives 3/1123 A-D to 3/1190 A-C, 1967 (Box 262)
  - Negatives 3/1191A-B to 3/1285, 1967 (Box 263)
  - Negatives 3/1286 to 3/1371A-C, 1967 (Box 264)
  - Negatives 3/1372A-B to 4/1435, 1967 (Box 265)
  - Negatives 3/1436A-B to 2/1523A-C, 1967 (Box 266)
  - Negatives 3/1524A-G to 3/1576A-B, 1967 (Box 267)
  - Negatives 2/1577A-E to 3/1655, 1967-1968 (Box 268)
  - Negatives 3/1656 to 2/1716A-K, 1968 (Box 269)
  - Negatives 2/1717 A-G to 3/1784, 1968 (Box 270)
  - Negatives 3/1785 A-B to 3/1869, 1968 (Box 271)
  - Negatives 2/1879 A-C to 3/1939 A-B, 1968 (Box 272)
  - Negatives 2/1940 A-E to 4/2011, 1968 (Box 273)
  - Negatives 4/2012 to 3/2086 A-G, 1968 (Box 274)
  - Negatives 3/2090 A-D to 3/2163 A-B, 1968 (Box 275)
  - Negatives 2/2164 A-D to 2/2241 A-D, 1968 (Box 276)
  - Negatives 3/2242 A-B to 3/2306 A-C, 1968-1969 (Box 277)
  - Negatives 3/2307 to 3/2379, 1969 (Box 278)
  - Negatives 3/2388 to 2/2463, 1969 (Box 279)
  - Negatives 3/2464 A-B to 2/2552 A-B, 1969 (Box 280)
  - Negatives 3/2553 A-E to 3/2662 A-G, 1969 (Box 281)
  - Negatives 3/2664 A-B to 3/2745 A-B, 1969 (Box 282)
  - Negatives 3/2746 A-B to 4/2835, 1969-1970 (Box 283)
  - Negatives 3/2836 A-B to 3/2920, 1970 (Box 284)
  - Negatives 4/2921 to 4/3000, 1970 (Box 285)
  - Negatives 3/3026 to 3/3007 A-C, 1970 (Box 286)
  - Negatives 2/3082 A-C to 4/3165, 1970 (Box 287)
  - Negatives 4/3166 to 3/3240 H-J, 1970-1971 (Box 288)
  - Negatives 4/3241 to 2/3319 A-P, 1971 (Box 289)
  - Negatives 3/3320 to 2/3400 A-C, 1971 (Box 290)
  - Negatives 3/3401 A-B to 2/3470 L-N, 1971 (Box 291)
  - Negatives 3/3471 A-B to 3/3548, 1971-1972 (Box 292)
  - Negatives 2/3549 A-B to 2/3619 A-G 3/3619 H, 1972 (Box 293)
  - Negatives 2/3620 A-B to 2/3697 A-C, 1972 (Box 294)
  - Negatives 3/3698 A-C - 3/3780, 1972 (Box 295)
  - Negatives 3/3781 A-B to 3/3873, 1972 (Box 296)
  - Negatives 3/3874 A-B to 3/3983, 1972-1973 (Box 297)
  - Negatives 3/2984 A-I to 3/4065, 1973 (Box 298)
  - Negatives 3/4066 to 3/4169, 1973 (Box 299)
  - Negatives 3/4170 A-C to 3/4275, 1973-1974 (Box 300)
  - Negatives 3/4276 A-B to 3/4325 A-B, 1974 (Box 301)
  - Negatives 3/4326 A-B to 3/4404, 1974 (Box 302)
  - Negatives 3/4405 to 2/4475, 1974 (Box 303)
  - Negatives 2/4476 to 2/4565, 1974 (Box 304)
  - Negatives 3/4566 A-B to 3/4646, 1974-1975 (Box 305)
  - Negatives 4/4647 to 3/4746, 1975 (Box 306)
  - Negatives 3/4747 A-B to 3/4818 A-J, 1975 (Box 307)
  - Negatives 3/4820 A-D to 3/4932, 1975 (Box 308)
  - Negatives 3/4933 to 4/5029, 1975-1976 (Box 309)
  - Negatives 4/5030 to 3/5123 A-D, 1976 (Box 310)
  - Negatives 3/5124 A-H to 3/5207 A-C, 1976 (Box 311)
  - Negatives 3/5208 A-B to 3/5322, 1976-1977 (Box 312)
  - Negatives 3/5323 to 4/5417, 1977 (Box 313)
  - Negatives 4/5418 to 3/5490 A-E, 1977 (Box 314)
  - Negatives 3/5491 A-J to 3/5579, 1977 (Box 315)
  - Negatives 3/5580 A-B to 3/5673, 1977-1978 (Box 316)
  - Negatives 3/5674 to 4/5750, 1978 (Box 317)
  - Negatives 4/5751 to 3/5820 A-B, 1978 (Box 318)
  - Negatives 2/5821 to 3/5908 A-B, 1978 (Box 319)
  - Negatives 3/5909 A-F to 3/5996 A-F, 1979 (Box 320)
  - Negatives 3/5997 A-C to 3/6060 J-S, 1979 (Box 321)
  - Negatives 3/6061 A-H to 3/6134, 1979 (Box 322)
  - Negatives 3/6135 to 3/6219 A-B, 1979 (Box 323)
  - Negatives 3/6220 to 3/6314, 1979-1980 (Box 324)
  - Negatives 3/6315 to 3/6398, 1980 (Box 325)
  - Negatives 3/6399 to 3/6468 F-K, 1980 (Box 326)
  - Negatives 3/6469 to 3/6547, 1980 (Box 327)
  - Negatives 3/6548 to 3/6647, 1980-1981 (Box 328)
  - Negatives 3/6648 to 3/6720, 1981 (Box 329)
  - Negatives 3/6721 to 3/6789 A-H, 1981 (Box 330)
  - Negatives 3/6790 A-C to 3/6870, 1981 (Box 331)
  - Negatives 3/6871 A-D to 3/6933 G-K, 1981 (Box 332)
  - Negatives 3/6834 A-D to 3/7010 A-E, 1981 (Box 333)
  - Negatives 3/7011 to 3/7120, 1981-1982 (Box 334)
  - Negatives 3/7121 to 3/7190, 1982 (Box 335)
  - Negatives to 3/7191 to 3/7271 A-H, 1982 (Box 336)
  - Negatives 3/7272 A-H to 4/7348 A-C, 1982 (Box 337)
  - Negatives 3/7349 A-H to 3/7419, 1982 (Box 338)
  - Negatives 3/7420 A-F to 3/7507, 1982 (Box 339)
  - Negatives 3/7508 A-B to 3/7603, 1982-1983 (Box 340)
  - Negatives 2/7604 A-D to 3/7696, 1983 (Box 341)
  - Negatives 3/7697 A-D to 3/7750, 1983 (Box 342)
  - Negatives 3/7751 to 3/7840 A-B, 1983 (Box 343)
  - Negatives 3/7841 A-E to 3/7915 A-B, 1983 (Box 344)
  - Negatives 3/7916 to 3/8000, 1983 (Box 345)
  - Negatives 3/8001 to 3/8061 F-J, 1983 (Box 346)
  - Negatives 3/8062 to 4/8125, 1983-1984 (Box 347)
  - Negatives 3/8126 A-B to 3/8220, 1984 (Box 348)
  - Negatives 3/8221 A-D to 3/8290, 1984 (Box 349)
  - Negatives 3/8291 A-B to 3/8362 A-H, 1984 (Box 350)
  - Negatives 3/8363 A-E to 4/8442, 1984 (Box 351)
  - Negatives 3/8444 to 4/8492, 1984 (Box 352)
  - Negatives 4/8493 to 4/8567, 1984 (Box 353)
  - Negatives 3/8568 to 3/8636 A-B, 1984 (Box 354)
  - Negatives 3/8637 to 3/8708 A-C, 1984-1985 (Box 355)
  - Negatives 3/8709 A-B to 4/8789, 1985 (Box 356)
  - Negatives 3/8790 A-D to 3/8861, 1985 (Box 357)
  - Negatives 3/8862 A-B to 3/8932, 1985 (Box 358)
  - Negatives 3/8933 A-B to 3/8998 A-E, 1985 (Box 359)
  - Negatives 3/8998 F-J to 3/9067 A-F, 1985 (Box 360)
  - Negatives 3/9067 G-M to 3/9105 A-B, 1985 (Box 361)
  - Negatives 3/9106 to 85-9151 L-P, 1985 (Box 362)
  - Negatives 85-9151 Q-U to 3/9204, 1985 (Box 363)
  - Negatives 3/9205 A-D to 3/9251, 1985 (Box 364)
  - Negatives 3/9252 A-C to 3/9314, 1985 (Box 365)
  - Negatives 3/9315 A-B to 4/9379, 1985-1986 (Box 366)
  - Negatives 3/9380 A-B to 3/9462 A-B, 1986 (Box 367)
  - Negatives 3/9463 A-C to 3/9532, 1986 (Box 368)
  - Negatives 3/9533 to 86-9565 6R-6Z, 1986 (Box 369)
  - Negatives 86-9565 7A-7M to 86-9620 A-F, 1986 (Box 370)
  - Negatives 9621 A-B to 86-9665 A-D, 1986 (Box 371)
  - Negatives 86-9666 A-B to 86FY-018 A-F, 1986 (Box 372)
  - Negatives 86FY-019 A-F to 86FY-083 A-D, 1986 (Box 373)
  - Negatives 86FY-085 to 86FY-138 A-B, 1986 (Box 374)
  - Negatives 86FY-139 to 86FY-203 M-R, 1986 (Box 375)
  - Negatives 86FY-203 S-X to 86FY-255 A-C, 1986-1987 (Box 376)
  - Negatives 86FY-256 A-E to 86FY-314 A-G, 1987 (Box 377)
  - Negatives 86FY-314 H-O to 86FY-383 A-D, 1987 (Box 378)
  - Negatives 86FY-384 A-B to 86FY-439 A-D, 1987 (Box 379)
  - Negatives 86FY-440 A-E to 86FY-483 F-K, 1987 (Box 380)
  - Negatives 86FY-484 A-D to 87-012, 1987 (Box 381)
  - Negatives 87-013 to 87-077, 1987 (Box 382)
  - Negatives 87-079 to 87-130 A-C, 1987 (Box 383)
  - Negatives 87-131 A-G to 87-174 A-B, 1987 (Box 384)
  - Negatives 87-176 A-E to 87-236 U-Z, 1987-1988 (Box 385)
  - Negatives 87-236 AA-II to 87-289 A-D, 1988 (Box 386)
  - Negatives 87-290 to 87-354 A-F, 1988 (Box 387)
  - Negatives 87-355 A-B to 87-409 A-E, 1988 (Box 388)
  - Negatives 87-409 F-I to 87-466 A-D, 1988 (Box 389)
  - Negatives 87-467 A-D to 87-519 K-N, 1988 (Box 390)
  - Negatives 87-519 O-V to 88-008 A-F, 1988 (Box 391)
  - Negatives 88-009 A-C to 88-048 A-I, 1988 (Box 392)
  - Negatives 88-050 A-B to 88-101 A-D, 1988 (Box 393)
  - Negatives 88-102 G-K to 88-156, 1988 (Box 394)
  - Negatives 88-155 A-C to 88-217 A-B, 1988-1989 (Box 395)
  - Negatives 88-218 A-D to 88-260 A-B, 1989 (Box 396)
  - Negatives 88-261 to 88-312 A-F, 1989 (Box 397)
  - Negatives 88-313 A-D to 88-354 E-H, 1989 (Box 398)
  - Negatives 88-354 A-D to 88-395 A-F, 1989 (Box 399)
  - Negatives 88-399 F-J to 88-445 G-M, 1989 (Box 400)
  - Negatives 88-446 P-Q to 89-026 A-F, 1989 (Box 401)
  - Negatives 89-027 A-D to 89-093 A-B, 1989 (Box 402)
  - Negatives 89-094 to 89-159 A-B, 1989 (Box 403)
  - Negatives 89-161 A-E to 89-200 P-Q, 1989-1990 (Box 404)
  - Negatives 89-201 A-B to 89-243 D-F, 1990 (Box 405)
  - Negatives 89-244 M-N to 89-289 A-B, 1990 (Box 406)
  - Negatives 89-290 A-D to 89-360 A17-22, 1990 (Box 407)
  - Negatives 89-360 B1-8 to 89-370 A-E2, 1990 (Box 408)
  - Negatives 89-370 P-U2 to 89-399 A-G, 1990 (Box 409)
  - Negatives 89-400 to 89-458 A-E, 1990 (Box 410)
  - Negatives 89-458 F-I to 90-024 A-D, 1990-1992 (Box 411)
  - Negatives 90-025 A-B to 90-102, 1990 (Box 412)
  - Negatives 90-103 A-B to 90-155, 1990 (Box 413)
  - Negatives 90-156 F-K to 90-229 E-G, 1990-1991 (Box 414)
  - Negatives 90-230 A-B to 90-312 A-E, 1991 (Box 415)
  - Negatives 90-313 to 90-355 A-E, 1991 (Box 416)
  - Negatives 90-356 A-C to 90-413 A-E, 1991 (Box 417)
  - Negatives 90-414 A-D to 90-451 C-D, 1991 (Box 418)
  - Negatives 90-452 to 90-524, 1991 (Box 419)
  - Negatives 91-002 A-E to 91-038 A-D, 1991 (Box 420)
  - Negatives 91-039 to 91-088 F-I, 1991 (Box 421)
  - Negatives 91-089 A-D to 91-155 T-X, 1991 (Box 422)
  - Negatives 91-155 Y-AA to 91-197 F-I, 1991-1992 (Box 423)
  - Negatives 91-198 to 91-273 A-C, 1992 (Box 424)
  - Negatives 91-274 A-C to 91-342 A-D, 1992 (Box 425)
  - Negatives 91-343 A-F to 91-400, 1992 (Box 426)
  - Negatives 91-401 A-B to 91-450 A-E, 1992 (Box 427)
  - Negatives 91-451 to 91-520 L-N, 1992 (Box 428)
  - Negatives 91-521 to 92-065 A-B, 1992 (Box 429)
  - Negatives 92-066 to 92-137, 1992 (Box 430)
  - Negatives 92-138 A-B to 92-224 A-E, 1992-1993 (Box 431)
  - Negatives 92-225 to 92-302 A-B, 1993 (Box 432)
  - Negatives 92-303 F-G to 92-362 H-K, 1993 (Box 433)
  - Negatives 92-363 A-E to 92-410 K-Q, 1993 (Box 434)
  - Negatives 92-411 A-E to 92-466 A-D, 1993 (Box 435)
  - Negatives 92-467 A-B to 92-533 A-B, 1993 (Box 436)
  - Negatives 92-534 A-D to 92-534 V10-Y10, 1992 (Box 437)
  - Negatives 92-534 F7-G7 to 92-577 E-H, 1992-1993 (Box 438)
  - Negatives 93-002 A-D to 93-004 M-O, 1993 (Box 439)
  - Negatives 93-044 P-R to 93-094 A-B, 1993 (Box 440)
  - Negatives 93-096 A-D to 93-151, 1993 (Box 441)
  - Negatives 93-152 to 93-229 F-K, 1993-1994 (Box 442)
  - Negatives 93-229 L-O to 93-306 A-E, 1994 (Box 443)
  - Negatives 93-306 F-J to 93-349 A-D, 1994 (Box 444)
  - Negatives 93-351 A-C to 93-401, 1994 (Box 445)
  - Negatives 93-402 A-B to 93-436 V-X, 1994 (Box 446)
  - Negatives 93-436 Y-BB to 93-468 G1-K1, 1994 (Box 447)
  - Negatives 93-469 A-B to 94-009 A-C, 1994 (Box 448)
  - Negatives 94-010 A-C to 94-077 A-C, 1994 (Box 449)
  - Negatives 94-078 A-B to 94-154 S-W, 1994 (Box 450)
  - Negatives 94-156 A-B to 94-209 D-F, 1994 (Box 451)
  - Negatives 94-210 A-B to 94-271 XX-ZZ, 1994-1995 (Box 452)
  - Negatives 94-272 A-C to 94-303 A-B, 1995 (Box 453)
  - Negatives 94-307 A-C to 94-342 A-C, 1995 (Box 454)
  - Negatives 94-343 A-C to 94-372 D-E, 1995 (Box 455)
  - Negatives 94-373 A-C to 94-406 ZZ-DDD, 1995 (Box 456)
  - Negatives 94-406 EEE-HHH to 94-451 A-B, 1995 (Box 457)
  - Negatives 94-452 A-C to 94-487 A-C, 1995 (Box 458)
  - Negatives 94-487 D-F to 94-516 A-B, 1995 (Box 459)
  - Negatives 94-518 A-C to 95-015 D-G, 1995 (Box 460)
  - Negatives 95-016 A-C to 95-059 D, 1995 (Box 461)
  - Negatives 95-061 A to 95-122 D-E, 1995 (Box 462)
  - Negatives 95-124 A-C to 95-173 D, 1995 (Box 463)
  - Negatives 95-174 A-C to 95-234 A-B, 1995-1996 (Box 464)
  - Negatives 95-235 A-C to 95-281 A-F, 1996 (Box 465)
  - Negatives 95-282 A-G to 95-293, 1992-1996 (Box 466)
  - Negatives 95-294 to 95-319 S, 1990-1996 (Box 467)
  - Negatives 95-320 A-C to 95-377 A-C, 1996 (Box 468)
  - Negatives 95-378 A to 95-429 D-E, 1996 (Box 469)
  - Negatives 95-430 A-B to 95-472 A-B, 1996 (Box 470)
  - Negatives 95-473 A-B to 95-512 S-U, 1996 (Box 471)
  - Negatives 95-512 V-X to 95-553 D, 1994-1996 (Box 472)
  - Negatives 95-559 A to 96-018 J-L, 1996 (Box 473)
  - Negatives 96-018 N to 96-085 G-H, 1996 (Box 474)
  - Negatives 96-086 A-B to 96-155 A, 1996 (Box 475)
  - Negatives 96-156 A to 96-222 A-C, 1996-1997 (Box 476)
  - Negatives 96-223 A-C to 96-277 A-B, 1997 (Box 477)
  - Negatives 96-278 A-B to 96-346 J-K, 1997 (Box 478)
  - Unprocessed Negatives (Box Missing, possibly does not exist), 1997 (Box 478a)
  - Negatives 96-347 A-C to 96-384 D-F, 1997 (Box 478b)